Preliminary Guide to the Robert Ward Papers, 1950s-2012 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2013-0014), undated, (44 boxes)
  - Recordings, (34 audio cassettes) (Box 30)
  - Recordings, (34 audio cassettes) (Box 31)
  - Recordings, (34 audio cassettes) (Box 32)
  - Recordings, (34 audio cassettes) (Box 33)
  - Recordings, (34 audio cassettes) (Box 34)
  - Recordings, (34 audio cassettes) (Box 35)
  - Recordings, (34 audio cassettes) (Box 36)
  - Recordings, (34 audio cassettes) (Box 37)
  - Recordings, (34 audio cassettes) (Box 38)
  - Recordings, (34 VHS tapes) (Box 39)
  - Recordings, (18 VHS tapes, 8 Umatic tapes) (Box 40)
  - Recordings, (38 7" reel recordings) (Box 41)
  - Recordings, (28 VHS tapes) (Box 42)
  - Recordings, (46 CDs) (Box 43)
  - Recordings, (54 CDs) (Box 44)
  - Recordings, (25 LPs, 7 5" reel recordings) (Box 45)
  - Recordings, (14 10" reel recordings) (Box 46)